BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 511-516 (Box 75)
  - Board of Adjustment - North Pacific Department, 1963-1974 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - North Pacific Department - By-Laws, 1963-1974 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- 517-end (Box 76)
  - Canadian Pacific - Merchandise Service System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1971 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - System Board of Adjustment 517 - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    April 5-7, 1971. Bound.
  - System Board of Adjustment 517 - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    May 13-15, 1970. Bound.
  - System Board of Adjustment 517 - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    May 27-30, 1969. Bound.
  - System Board of Adjustment 517 - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    April 23-26, 1968. Bound.
  - System Board of Adjustment 517 - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    May 30-June 2, 1967. Bound.
  - System Board of Adjustment 517 - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - System Board of Adjustment 517 - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    May 9-11, 1972. Bound.
  - Boards of Adjustment - Canadian Pacific Express, 1965-1966 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Meeting Minutes, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    May 9-11, 1966
  - Pan-American Airways System Board of Adjustment - By-Laws, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Pan American World Airways Incorporated, 1966-1969 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Pan American World Airways, Incorporated, 1965-1966 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Pan American World Airways, Incorporated: Appeal of John Le Bright, Junior to Grand Lodge Convention, 1966-1967 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Washington, DC Area Pan American World Airways District Board of Adjustment, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Caribair, Caribbean Atlantic Airlines, Incorporated District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1970 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Board of Adjustment - Caribbean Atlantic Airlines, 1963-1970 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Canadian National Railways - By-Laws, Dues, Salaries, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    October 5, 1959
  - System Division - Erie-Lackawanna, 1969-1974 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    April 3 1969-September 20 1974
  - System Division - Soo Line, 1969-1975 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    April 3, 1969-March 1, 1975
- 263 - 0; 271 - 0 (Box 77)
  - Disaster Relief (Financial Assistance), 1963-1966 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Committee for International Economic Growth, 1960-1961 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Conferences - Annual Organization: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairman, et al (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Conferences - Annual Organization: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et al. - Papers Presented, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    June 9-11, 1964
  - Conferences - Educational (Western, Eastern, and Southeastern), 1965 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Western: March 10, 1965 in Chicago, Illinois. Eastern: March 16, 1965 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Southeastern: March 18, 1965 in Atlanta, Georgia. Package included.
  - Conferences - Annual Educational Conference: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et al., 1966 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    Includes package. October 25-26, 1966.
  - Conferences - Annual Conference on Organization: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et al., 1964 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Conferences - Annual Organization: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et al., 1968 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    April 22-24, 1968. Includes package.
  - Conferences - Annual Organization: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen et al., 1969 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    October 27-29, 1969.
  - Conferences - Annual Organization: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et al., 1969 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    May 6-8, 1969. Includes package.
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1974 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    April-November 19, 1974. Includes bound materials.
- 0 (Box 78)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1968-1971 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    September 1966-December 1967
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Economic Policy, 1957-1970 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    May 1957-1970
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - General Board, 1957-1968 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - George Meany Foundation, 1962-1969 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Fund Committee, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Publicity Committee and Committee on Public Relations, 1956-1968 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Ladies Auxiliary, 1961-1964 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - William Green Memorial Fund, 1953-1963 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, 1959-1967 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Project Hope, 1960-1964 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    October 1960-April 1964
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Scientific, Professional, and Cultural Employees (SPACE), 1966-1969 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    1966-1969
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Liaison Committee, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee for the United Nations, 1962-1963 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- 0 (Box 79)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    October 1973-March 1974
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    January 1973-September 1973. Includes bound materials.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1972-1973 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    January 1972-January 1973
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1969-1971 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    January 1969-December 1971. Includes package.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1967-1968 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    January 1967-December 1968. Includes bound pamphlets.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1966 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1964-1965 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    March 1964-December 1965
- 0; 6 (Box 80)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    April 20, 1966-August 31, 1966
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    December 1, 1965-March 7 1966
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    March 8-April 19, 1966
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    January-November 1965
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    April-December 1964
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Civil Rights Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    January 1, 1961-March 31, 1964
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Seventh Constitution Convention, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    December 7, 1967. Includes bound materials,
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Eighth Constitutional Convention, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    October 2, 1969.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Sixth Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    December 9, 1965
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Labor-Management Committee for Industrial Peace, 1960-1971 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Conference on Transportation Trades, 1967-1969 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Human Resources Development Institute, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    July 1, 1971
  - Labor Organizations - Maritime Trades Department, 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Maritime Trades Department, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    January 1968-May 1969
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Maritime Trades Department, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    July-December 1967
- 6-29 (Box 81)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Maritime Trades Department, 1964-1967 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    January 1964-June 1967
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Central Labor Councils, 1958-1971 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Per Capita Tax, 1960-1962 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Organizers, 1933-1962 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Executive Council, 1963-1972 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    March 15, 1963-December 1972
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Statements of Executive Council, 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Statements of Executive Council, 1966-1968 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Executive Council: Labor Advisory Committee to Labor Department on Landrum-Griffin Act and Taft-Hartley Act, 1961-1965 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Executive Council, 1972-1973 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    December 1972-July 1973
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Report on Examination, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    January 1-June 30, 1973
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Political Program, 1960-1968 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Organization, 1962-1969 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- 60-80 (Box 82)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Press Releases (News), 1966-1970 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Union Industries Show, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    May 19-24, 1967.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Union Industries Show (Booth), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    May 21-27, 1970
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Union Industries Show, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    June 21-26, 1968
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Union Industries Show Exhibitors' Information, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Official News Volume 11, Number 4, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    April 1967. Bound.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Industries Show, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    May 19-24, 1967. Bound.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Industries Show Exhibitors' Information, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    May 19- 24, 1967. Bound.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department: Union Industries Show, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    April 29-May 4, 1966
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Industries Show Exhibitors' Information, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    April 29- May 4, 1966. Bound.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Labor Press, 1950-1971 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    May 1950- June 1971
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - International Labor Committee (International Affairs), 1963-1973 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    January 1963-May 1973
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - National Legislative Council, 1948-1967 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- 80-87 (Box 83)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - International Association of Machinists Complaint Against Brotherhood of Railway Carmen, United Air Lines, Representation Election, National Mediation Board Case, 1947-1963 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Merger, 1955-1958 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    December 1955- 1958. Includes bound materials.
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1956-1973 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    1956-June 1973
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1963-1970 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Political Education (COPE) Report, 1956-1967 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Aviation Legislative Committee, 1956-1964 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Legislative Conference, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    January 11-14, 1965
  - Special Executive Council Subcommittee on Labor Legislation, 1958-1967 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Ethical Practices, 1959-1964 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Ethical Practices, Bakery and Confectionery Workers, 1959- 1961 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    September 1959-July 1961
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Ethical Practices, United Garment Workers of America, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- 273 - 0; 276 - 0 (Box 84)
  - Canadian Labor Congress, 1965-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    Includes bound materials
  - Trades and Labor Congress of Canada - Affiliation, 1960-1962 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Canadian Labour Congress (Trades and Labor Congress of Canada) - Dual Organizations, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Protest and Request for Suspension Cancellation of LCL Freight, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight, 1962-1964 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - To amend Rule 33 and Rule 33(e), 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Rulings, Orders, etcetera, 1958-1965 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    May 1958-1965
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1966-1969 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - New York Central Transport Company for permission to engage in over-the-road trucking without restriction at any point along the lines of the New York Central System, 1960-1961 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    1960-October 15, 1961
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - New York Central Transport Company for permission to engage in over-the-road trucking without restriction at any point along the lines of the New York Central System, 1961-1964 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    October 16, 1961-July 1964
- 0; 277 - 0 (Box 85)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Accident Reports, 1958-1970 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - American Barge Line, 1952-1962 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Bessemer and Lake Erie), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Boston and Maine), 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Central of New Jersey), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Miscellaneous), 1961-1969 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Chesapeake and Ohio), 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Chicago and Eastern Illinois), 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Chicago and North Western), 1961-1963 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Columbus and Greenville), 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Delaware and Hudson), 1963 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Denver and Rio Grande Western), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton), 1963 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Durham and Southern), 1963 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Erie-Lackawanna), 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Green Bay and Western), 1962-1963 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio), 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (High Point, Thomasville, and Denton), 1964 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Lehigh Valley), 1965 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Long Island), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Maine Central), 1964 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Missouri Pacific), 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (New York Central), 1961-1964 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (New York, Chicago, and Saint Louis), 1961-1964 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (New York and Long Branch), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (New York, New Haven, and Hartford), 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville), 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Norfolk and Western), 1963-1970 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Pennsylvania), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    April 1962-1964
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Pennsylvania), 1961-1962 (Box 85, Folder 30)
    1961-March 1962
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines), 1961-1965 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Pittsburgh, Charters, and Youghiogheny), 1963 (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Pittsburgh and Lake Erie), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Quanah, Acme, and Pacific), 1964 (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Reading), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Protest and Request for Suspension, Cancellation of LCL Freight (Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac), 1962 (Box 85, Folder 36)